[Music]
I don't want to come to any Hasty
conclusions at this point is it a
literal War on Christmas this is why the
media always drives me nuts instead of
reporting the news they just love to
guess you know they they get into this
game of of speculation and conjecture or
as I like to call it premature
conjul Santa not everybody wants guns
but you know these are kind of the times
we live in oh don't tell me about the
times I keep up with the times heck I
call Donna Joyce now because she
identifies as a woman like I you know I
I I'm cool I'm cool with whateves okay
white sounding names I don't know what
that means you are more likely to get
hired that's up yeah is that true you
think I don't know Larry yeah Larry I
got a job oh my
God
Larry and Robin hey America Larry
Wilmore here if you like the nightly
show on Comedy Central like us on
Facebook too just don't poke me I do not
like being poked you can Candy Crush me